And the place death, considering who thou art,
if any of my chins may find thee here.
With love's light wings did I overperch these walls,
for stony limits cannot hold love out,
and what love can do that dares love attempt.
Therefore thy kinsmen are no led to me.
If they do see thee, they will murder thee.
There's more peril in thine eye than in their swords.
Look thou the sweetest, and I am proof against their enmity.
Incredible performance! You had me in tears!
This is my husband, Qin Jin.
Ah! The detective!
Oh, I am.
I am.
And I am.
You are.
I am.
Ah, the detective, of course. She speaks highly of you.
She's too kind. It's Da Shuai, yes?
No, no, no. Please call me Shuang Shuai.
You've taught her so much. I'm grateful.
No, Lisa's star power is all her own.
I just wish more people appreciated your art these days. It's a shame.
Hey, don't forget. You said you'd support me.
And I do.
Oh, right. How was the new venue you went to look at together? Cheaper? That'd be nice.
The, uh, venue, yeah. We haven't found anything yet.
We looked at the old plant on Tiantong Road a few days ago, remember?
Right. I figured we could check it out, but no luck. We could never afford it.
The old plant? Odd. I heard they converted it to office spaces.
There's a stage, too?
Yes. There's some extra room hidden in the back, away from the offices.
It's kind of a secret. Join us for dinner?
You go on ahead. No one likes a third wheel.
Captain Chen.
Hello?
Captain!
Chen.
I didn't see you. Heard you with Xiao Li. How's it going?
I'm fine, but I heard you haven't been doing too hot lately. That's why I'm here.
Sure enough, you're like a zombie.
Well, maybe that's what I get for working late.
I'm showing my age. Happens to the best.
Take a break. Your wife probably misses you.
She must get pretty lonely at home.
My girl's the same. Says I work too much.
Your wedding's around the corner. She'll make a good bride. You're a lucky man.
Huh? Forget me. We're talking about you.
My wife is...
Trust me. Just stay single.
Nah. I'm a lost cause. I'm too used to this life.
And my body's turning on me. After a few performances, my back is all kinds of sore.
Sometimes, I can barely stand up straight.
She's busy.
You're insane. What are you talking about?
I can still fit into it.
Sure, I gained a few pounds after the wedding.
But a little dieting will fix that.
Chen Jin, slow down.
We've had enough.
We're fools.
Why do we work so hard?
What's the point of it?
Our work doesn't keep our wives faithful.
Say, Xiaoli.
Tell me.
Who was to blame for that?
Hmm?
Come on.
Was it me or him?
Well, speak up.
Or was it her fault?
Yes.
Nothing to say?
Chen Jin.
Listen.
There's something you should know.
It's not me.
Shh.
Sir, why are you here?
Brief me.
You've got a lot going on.
We can handle the case.
It's fine.
The deceased are a married couple.
Li Ulan, 38.
Li Fan, 42.
Their neighbor called in.
Told dispatch the husband was beating the wife.
Deng is his name.
Nobody answered when our officers arrived.
They found the bodies after forcing the door open.
No vitals.
Based on the scene, we think the couple accidentally killed each other during an argument.
Not surprising.
They were fighting with a hammer and a kitchen knife.
That guy's the neighbor.
I'm sorry.
What was that?
I got distracted.
Also, the deceased had two kids we brought in.
The boy's quite protective.
You'll see.
The captain.
Captain.
You're safe now.
What happened to your parents?
I killed them both.
You live with him. Really?
There was this one time. You told me to become a hunter.
I did.
Do you think I'm one now?
More like a wild beast.
Pop quiz. Do you know the difference between the two?
Wild beasts are vicious. Hunters are smarter.
Nope. The beasts only kill when they're hungry. Not true with hunters.
Mr. Liu!
I'm positive about one thing. You'll have the chance to be a hunter in the near future.
It's almost time. We must leave or you'll be late.
Am I going to see you again?
I'm sure you will.
Gentlemen, can I help you with something?
Yes. Yu Jing asked me to come by.
Excuse me, sir. These men are looking for your father.
I'm the one who invited them. Let my guests in.
Please, enjoy.
Thanks.
Your father told me all that you've been through. It's awful.
Huh. I have you to thank for solving the mess with that woman.
So what can I do for you today?
Huh?
Who's this kid?
He looks weirdly familiar.
Yo. Have we met before?
Don't tell me you brought an idiot along.
Please, sir. No need for insults. Let's focus.
Insults?
Those keyboard warriors who constantly attack me are the only ones insulting people.
I heard you've helped my father in many ways.
Can you do me a favor, too?
I can send formal letters to those who defame you to scare them.
A warning.
You think that'd work?
You're not naive.
You know they wouldn't care.
I want the people who rally internet trash against me to shut up forever.
Be real with me.
I know you can make them disappear.
You are dé comprar.
Mr. Liu.
How do you jest?
You're drunk?
Nope. I already picked someone.
In that case, you shouldn't be asking me.
This will be up to my friend here.
So there is a brain floating around in there.
He's laughing. Does this mean he'll take the job?
He's laughing.
That teacher guy, he's got it real bad for the mother.
That told him to track since he's always dropping by.
I bet they're getting close.
That's what I've seen.
She's been trying you.
That makes you a cuckold.
How can a man stand such humiliation?
Everyone's laughing at you behind your back.
Oh!
Ha-ha!
Ah!
Ah-ha-ha-ha!
Ha-ha-ha!
Oh, my God.